I have taken out the robber device,
listen, one of its devices is this and
subscribe to it, you can subscribe,
so this appointment is um hello hello
guys welcome to my channel my
name is and so guys how are you guys,
you all must be fine, so today's video is going to be about
a very simple topic and I
mean as you understood that I want to
talk about it, subscribe and subscribe and it becomes
very difficult to subscribe, then I mean
ask the school, so today I will
use it, I mean use it and as
I told you that I will give it in today's video,
now you can watch such videos
and my insurance is from this
company, this which I have taken,
my experience with this company is very
good and Meghnad is going to
subscribe to our GPS device and this is
that I had done it in it, you know
that you all have this, after that it is
not possible for us, but subscribe, we will
subscribe to this company, so I got it done
with this, in the same
Shubhesh cheers to me device  The
criminal Abhijit, neither I nor
anyone else used this device for this and I
need to subscribe for this, so
first I will take out my device and show it to you, it
forgets that it is soft in it,
I will take it out, now
I have bought this device, see this device
and you can subscribe to it, so
now the biggest problem is that you
should buy it and subscribe to the channel
[laughs]
subscribe
thanks for the mod, I don't have to pay anything,
otherwise if you buy the device
yourself, you have to subscribe early while paying this cost of Rs 5000, if you had to
appoint hatred then it will
automatically subscribe to me, let
me tell you one more thing that
like subscribe subscribe subscribe to the mobile
application, we will
talk about where the mobile is and will talk
about it, we will install that application and
discuss about them, so let's start,
first of all I will open it,
see, this is its
entire home screen and in the home screen, the
address is coming that where my car is currently
parked, this is the length  Mark, I am
solving it for you in the map, after this it notifies you about the
travel kilometer, how much charge is there in the battery right now, the
rest is shared etc.
and there is the vehicle
number, along with this here we have this
right side effect, we
will click on it, there is settings,
in the settings you will see for
which things it gives alerts, so see,
like in the search engine, then
click on the configure of speed metering,
you can set here that if
my car goes up, then after how much
time it keeps
alerting you, if someone else is
driving the car apart from you, it will alert you about that thing also,
after that if I take out my device and someone turns on your
car, then
you will have a notification, you will get a question about someone
driving in a very rough manner, you will get a
question about that too, it will not be synchronized, you will
also get a question about servicing, your Pan
Sanjeev fans means that country
configuration means that life
is your owner of the house, you have a Jio function, like this,
this entire area is in blue, I mean
Jatin  It is set in kilometer by kilometer area,
you can set it to any number
but you can increase or
decrease it by any number of officers, that means
if your car goes out of that area then you will
automatically get a message and an email will go, the
rest is the previous summary etc. that overall
what did we drive, how much did we drive the car
etc. ignition off battery, I have told you, so I
click here on the front side
and it is
complete in the insurance activity, that you
need your car here on this day, that is
you know that I went to Ludhiana in another car, so
it is very rarely that I am able to
run it, so guys, see the complete summary
here, which line of yours,
how much did you drive your car and what is your condition on which day,
it tells that kilometer
and along with this I tell you the entire
tracking of that area, the entire area,
which line did you take from here to
here, so
you get to see all these benefits in this entire application, it is
of Taylor Swift and I tell you
that you do not get trapped and if you have any
problem anywhere, then you can directly click on this  You
can press the call button here by clicking, it
is fine directly but your car people will call you
and with this you can take your help
and I had shared a very
good story with you that once when the
chamber oil tank of my car broke down and
how I got help for it, I got Veena for free, I got
it
serviced for free, I
got a lot of things in which I have not seen that video,
I have the i button for it, now you
can go there and watch that video, so
guys you have seen the device and I have
also told you all the functions, I hope
you
liked the video, if you liked the video then
like it instead of sharing, subscribe to my channel,
behind you are for watching my
video by A
[sangeet]